Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
- Box: 68, folder: 18 (Box 68, Folder 18)
  - Item 47: Quarterly Report of NLRB General Counsel on Case Developments (Official Text), Publication (Box 68, Folder 18)
- Box: 68, folder: 19 (Box 68, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Collective Bargaining and the War Against Poverty, Publication (Box 68, Folder 19)
    By Arnold Orman. February 18, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Policy of the National Labor Relations Board Toward Current Changes and Developments in Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 68, Folder 19)
    By Howard W. Kleeb. October 23, 1963. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: "The Policy, the Purpose and the Philosophy of the NLRB as Revealed in Decision Trends", Publication (Box 68, Folder 19)
    By Frank W. McCulloch. October 28-29, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Procedures Employed by NLRB in Determining Policy, Publication (Box 68, Folder 19)
    By Frank W. McCulloch. August 11, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Litigant's Role and the Public Interest, Publication (Box 68, Folder 19)
    By Arnold Ordman. February 21, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Policy of the National Labor Relations Board Toward Current Changes and Developments in Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 68, Folder 19)
  - Item 7: What's Right with the Labor Board, Publication (Box 68, Folder 19)
    By Boyd Leeman. December 4, 1963. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Compulsion and Freedom in Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 68, Folder 19)
    By Frank W. McCulloch. March 8, 1963. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Then and Now (A Comparison of Two Summers), Publication (Box 68, Folder 19)
    By Ogden W. Fields. August 7. 1962. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: A Tale of Two Cities: or Law in Action, Publication (Box 68, Folder 19)
    By Frank W. McCulloch. August 7, 1962. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Jurisdictional Disputes Before the NLRB, Publication (Box 68, Folder 19)
    By Gerald A. Brown. September 17, 1962. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Inquiring Courts and the National Labor Relations Act, Publication (Box 68, Folder 19)
    By William Feldesman. August 7, 1962. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Employer Rights and Their Limitations During Union Organizational Campaigns, Publication (Box 68, Folder 19)
    By Howard W. Kleeb. January 29, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: An Administrative Agency in a Changing World, Publication (Box 68, Folder 19)
    By Gerald A. Brown. January 29, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Rules and Regulations and Statements of Procedure, Publication (Box 68, Folder 19)
    Amended October 22, 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Recommended Rules of Practice of the National Labor Relations Board, Publication (Box 68, Folder 19)
    July 28, 1960. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Labor Act Upside Down, Publication (Box 68, Folder 19)
    By Joseph E. Finley. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: NLRB Procedures and Economic Policy, Publication (Box 68, Folder 19)
  - Item 19: Information to Voters in Elections Conducted by the National Labor Relations Board, Publication (Box 68, Folder 19)
  - Item 20: The Job of the NLRB, Publication (Box 68, Folder 19)
    By John H. Fanning. March 2, 1962. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Changing NLRB Policies: 1953-1954, Publication (Box 68, Folder 19)
    By Fred Witney. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Organization and Procedure of the National Labor Relations Board, Publication (Box 68, Folder 19)
  - Item 23: Address before the Rutgers University Conference on the National Labor Relations Board in New Jersey, Publication (Box 68, Folder 19)
    By Jerome D. Fenton. September 30, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Reorganization Announced in NLRB Office of General Counsel, Publication (Box 68, Folder 19)
    February 13, 1960. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: The NLRB--What it is and What it is Not, Publication (Box 68, Folder 19)
    September 15, 1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: The New Labor Legislation and the Office of the General Counsel, Publication (Box 68, Folder 19)
    By Stuart Rothman. November 2, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Statement of the National Labor Relations Board, Publication (Box 68, Folder 19)
    By Paul M. Hertzog. February 24, 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Effecting Better Understanding Between Employers and NLRB Regional Offices, Publication (Box 68, Folder 19)
    By Theophil C. Kammholz. January 18, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: NLRB - Its Tools for Administrative Case-Handling, Publication (Box 68, Folder 19)
    By John H. Fanning. February 2, 1960. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Current Problems in the Administration of the Taft-Hartley Act, Publication (Box 68, Folder 19)
    March 12, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: NLRB Appoints Saul J. Jaffe as Associate Solicitor, Publication (Box 68, Folder 19)
  - Item 32: Board Member Joseph Alton Jenkins Names Chief Counsel, Publication (Box 68, Folder 19)
  - Item 33: NLRB Appoints Five Additional Trial Examiners, Publication (Box 68, Folder 19)
    April 12, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 34: William T. Evans Named Special Assistant to General Counsel, Publication (Box 68, Folder 19)
    July 5, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 35: Organization and Procedure of the National Labor Relations Board, Publication (Box 68, Folder 19)
  - Item 36: Improving Settlement Procedures at the National Labor Relations Board, Publication (Box 68, Folder 19)
    By Stuart Rothman. September 29, 1960. Item is in English.
  - Item 37: Address before the Rutgers University Conference on the National Labor Relations Board of New Jersey, Publication (Box 68, Folder 19)
    By Jerome D. Fenton. Septmber 30, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 38: The Role of the National Labor Relations Board in the Management-Labor Relationship Today, Publication (Box 68, Folder 19)
    By Theophil C. Kammholz. May 24, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 39: The Taft-Hartley Act Prevention or Cure in Labor Relations, Publication (Box 68, Folder 19)
    By Jerome D. Fenton. March 1, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 40: Hearing before a Committee on Labor and Public Welfare United States Senate, Publication (Box 68, Folder 19)
    May 9, 1963. Item is in English.
  - Item 41: The NLRB in Action, Publication (Box 68, Folder 19)
    By Frank W. McCulloch. April 19, 1962. Item is in English.
  - Item 42: Act, Board and Critics: A Few ABC's, Publication (Box 68, Folder 19)
    By William Feldesman. October 18, 1963. Item is in English.
  - Item 43: The National Labor Relations Board and Stare Decisis, Publication (Box 68, Folder 19)
    By John H. Fanning. March 5, 1963. Item is in English.
  - Item 44: An Administrative Agency in a Changing World, Publication (Box 68, Folder 19)
  - Item 45: The NLRB in Action, Publication (Box 68, Folder 19)
  - Item 46: Four Areas of the Developing Law - Resume and Rationale -, Publication (Box 68, Folder 19)
    By Stuart Rothman. February 15, 1963. Item is in English.
  - Item 47: Civil Liberties and the NLRB, Publication (Box 68, Folder 19)
  - Item 48: Problems of the National Labor Relations Board, Publication (Box 68, Folder 19)
- Box: 68, folder: 20 (Box 68, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: The Railway Labor Act and the National Mediation Board, Publication (Box 68, Folder 20)
    September 19, 1956. Item is in English.
- Box: 68, folder: 21 (Box 68, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Mediation Agreement, Cases A-7127 and A-7128 and Related Letters of Understanding, Dated November 20, 1964 between Railroads Represented by the National Railway Labor Conference and the Eastern, Western and Southeastern Carriers' Conference Committees, Publication (Box 68, Folder 21)
    November 20, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Mediation Agreement, Case No. A-7128 Dated February 7, 1965 between Railroads Represented by the National Railway Labor Conference and the Eastern, Western and Southeastern Carriers' Conference Committees, Publication (Box 68, Folder 21)
    February 7, 1965. Item is in English.
- Box: 68, folder: 22 (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Special Report from the National Right to Work Committee: "Casualties of a One-Man War", Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - Item 2: New York Journal of Commerce: As Business Leaders See It, Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
    June 9, 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Washington Daily News Clipping, Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
    May 26, 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Memorandum: Special Report to Member - No. 2, Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
    By E. S. Dillard. September 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Memorandum: Special Report - No. 1, Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
    September 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Right-to-Work Drive Goes On, Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - Item 7: Long-Time Union Man Brands Compulsion Un-American, Enemy of Free Workers, Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - Item 8: Why Well-Informed Americans Reject The Bogus "Free Rider" Complaint, Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - Item 9: Reprints from the National Right to Work Committee, Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - Item 10: The Documented Record on Which the Controversial Movie "And Women Must Weep" is Based, Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - Item 11: Senator Goldwater Sets the Record Straight on Right to Work, Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - Item 12: Forty-Four Words, Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
    By Reed Larson. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Should Union Membership be Compulsory or Voluntary?, Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - Item 14: The Proof of Right-to-Work Benefits, Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - Item 15: The Kennedy--Ervin Bill: Some of its Provisions, Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - Item 16: An Educatoinal Radio Series on Right to Work, Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - Item 17: WhyRight-to-Work Laws are Necessity, Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
    By Martin Lu. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: "The Secondary Boycott Issue", Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
    By Ray Clymer. March 14, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Why and How in Right-to-Work, Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
    By McLellan Smith. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: High Cost of Unionism, Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
    By Ludwig W. Freier. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Warning! Danger Ahead!, Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
    By Maurice R. Franks. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Complusory Union Membership: Un-Americanism at Work, Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - Item 23: Union Shopping, Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
    By Maurice R. Frank. March 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: State Right-to-Work Laws, Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - Item 25: The Economics of Right to Work, Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - Item 26: The Anatomy of a Wildcat, Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
    By Edward W. Greenfield. May 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Check-Off: labor bosses and working men, Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - Item 28: Right to Work, Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - Item 29: A Labor Government in America?, Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - Item 30: Blocking the Path of Union Partnership, Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - Item 31: The Right to Work: Americans Must Have the Right but not be Compelled to Join Labor Unions, Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - Item 32: Union Sources Admit:, Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - Item 33: Americans Believe-, Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - Item 34: "The Secondary Boycott Issue", Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
    By Ray Climer. Item is in English.
  - Item 35: The Voluntarism of Samuel Gompers, Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - Item 36: Loopholes in Their Logic: Facts Show Right to Work More Important Than Mere Political Issue, Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - Item 37: New Right to Work Leader Familiar With 'Union Shops', Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
    By N. Thorington. Item is in English.
  - Item 38: America's Choice: Right to Work or Compulsory Unionism, Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - Item 39: Compulsory Unionsim: The New Slavery, Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
    By Donald R. Richberg. Item is in English.
  - Item 40: Governors for Right to Work: Heading the Benefits of Right to Work Laws, Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - Item 41: Protestantism and the Right to Work, Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
    By Dr. Frederick Curtis Fowler. Item is in English.
  - Item 42: The "Union Shop"-Power in the Hands of Dictators, Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
    By John M. Mosberger. Item is in English.
  - Item 43: Pope John and The Right to Work, Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
    By Rev. John E. Coogan, S.J. Item is in English.
  - Item 44: The Meaning of "Laborism", Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
    By Lafayette A. Hooser. Item is in English.
  - Item 45: This Thing Fightens Me!, Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
    By Rev. Edward W. Greenfield. Item is in English.
  - Item 46: We, The UndersignedA message to American wage-earners, Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - Item 47: Progress Memo 1959, Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - Item 48: What Happened to Liberty and Justice for All?, Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - Item 49: Forced Union Membership, Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - Item 50: Should Union Membership Be Compulsory or Voluntary?, Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - Item 51: Forced Union Membership Steals Your Freedom, Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - Item 52: A Basic Right, Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - Item 53: The Right to Refrain: How and Why the Advocates of Compulsory Unionism were Beaten in 1965, Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - Item 54: The Legal and Moral Basis of Right to Work Laws: Legislative Restrictions Upon Union Security Agreements, Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
    By Mr. J. C. Gibson. Item is in English.
  - Item 55: Do Right to Work Laws Hurt or Help the Economy?, Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - Item 56: Economic Progress in Right to Work States, Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - Item 57: The Right to Refrain, Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
    By Hugh C. Newton. Item is in English.
  - Item 58: Griffin Bill Analysis, Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - Item 59: New Jobs - New Wealth - New Progress in the Right to Work States, Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - Item 60: Correspondance, Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - Item 61: Why I'm for Right-to-Work, Publication (Box 68, Folder 22)
    By Lafayetter A. Hooser. June 17, 1961. Item is in English.
- Box: 68, folder: 23 (Box 68, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Charts on Organization, Publication (Box 68, Folder 23)
- Box: 68, folder: 24 (Box 68, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Personnel Aministration at the Executive Level, Publication (Box 68, Folder 24)
  - Item 2: The Naval Manpower Information System, Publication (Box 68, Folder 24)
- Box: 68, folder: 25 (Box 68, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: A Network Flow Technique for Optimizing Personnel on Board by Pay Grade, Publication (Box 68, Folder 25)
    By Donald F. Hayter, Richard D. Conner. February 1966. Item is in English.
- Box: 68, folder: 26 (Box 68, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Earn, Learn, Serve, Publication (Box 68, Folder 26)
  - Item 2: Pogo: Welcome to the Beginning, Publication (Box 68, Folder 26)
  - Item 3: Pogo: Welcome to the Beginning, Publication (Box 68, Folder 26)
  - Item 4: The Story of the Neighborhood Youth Corps, Publication (Box 68, Folder 26)
- Box: 68, folder: 27 (Box 68, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Research Opportunities for Air Force Officers, Publication (Box 68, Folder 27)
- Box: 68, folder: 28 (Box 68, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: OEO News Summary, Publication (Box 68, Folder 28)
    October 27, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Statement by Donald Rumsfield on Legal Services Program, Publication (Box 68, Folder 28)
    July 14, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Statement by Donald Rumsfeld on Legal Services Program, Publication (Box 68, Folder 28)
  - Item 4: Office of Economic Opportunity 1968 Year-End Report, Publication (Box 68, Folder 28)
    January 7, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Office of Econommic Opportunity 1968 Year-End Report, Publication (Box 68, Folder 28)
  - Item 6: Office of Econommic Opportunity 1968 Year-End Report, Publication (Box 68, Folder 28)
  - Item 7: Community Action Program Guide, Volume I: Instructions for Applicants, Publication (Box 68, Folder 28)
    October 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Community Action and Urban Housing, Publication (Box 68, Folder 28)
    November 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: OEO News Summary, Publication (Box 68, Folder 28)
- Box: 68, folder: 29 (Box 68, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Economic Opportunity Act of 1964, as Amended, Publication (Box 68, Folder 29)
    August 20, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Community Action for Health: Family Planning, Publication (Box 68, Folder 29)
    October 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Community Education: Tutorial Programs, Publication (Box 68, Folder 29)
  - Item 4: Community Education: Tutorial Programs, Publication (Box 68, Folder 29)
  - Item 5: OEO Film Guide, Publication (Box 68, Folder 29)
  - Item 6: Adult Basic Education Program Fact Sheet, Publication (Box 68, Folder 29)
  - Item 7: Vista - Volunteer Corps of the War on Poverty Fact Sheet, Publication (Box 68, Folder 29)
  - Item 8: Job Corps Facts, Publication (Box 68, Folder 29)
  - Item 9: Quick Facts on the Programs of The Office of Economic Opportunity, Publication (Box 68, Folder 29)
  - Item 10: Small Business Loans Fact Sheet, Publication (Box 68, Folder 29)
  - Item 11: Adult Basic Education Program Fact Sheet, Publication (Box 68, Folder 29)
  - Item 12: Work Experience Fact Sheet, Publication (Box 68, Folder 29)
  - Item 13: The Foster Grandparent Program, Publication (Box 68, Folder 29)
  - Item 14: Community Action Program Fact Sheet, Publication (Box 68, Folder 29)
  - Item 15: Rural Family Loans Fact Sheet, Publication (Box 68, Folder 29)
  - Item 16: Programs for Migrants and Seasonal Farm Workers Fact Sheet, Publication (Box 68, Folder 29)
  - Item 17: Neighborhood Youth Corps Fact Sheet, Publication (Box 68, Folder 29)
  - Item 18: Work Study Program, Publication (Box 68, Folder 29)
  - Item 19: Upward Bound Fact Sheet, Publication (Box 68, Folder 29)
  - Item 20: Work Experience Fact Sheet, Publication (Box 68, Folder 29)
  - Item 21: Project Head Start Fact Sheet, Publication (Box 68, Folder 29)
  - Item 22: Fact Sheet for Women's Centers of the Job Corps, Publication (Box 68, Folder 29)
  - Item 23: Legal Services Fact Sheet, Publication (Box 68, Folder 29)
  - Item 24: Response to Senate Subcommittee Letter on Mississippi, Publication (Box 68, Folder 29)
    April 29, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Quick Facts on the Programs of the Office of Economic Opportunity, Publication (Box 68, Folder 29)
  - Item 26: Job Corps Facts, Publication (Box 68, Folder 29)
- Box: 69, folder: 1 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Guidelines, Publication (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Project Head Start and How You Can Help, Publication (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: You Have New Neighbors, Publication (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: You Have New Neighbors, Publication (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Manpower Management in the Office of Economic Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Office of Economic Opportunity, Publication (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Job Corps Centers, Communities Enjoy Good Relations, Publication (Box 69, Folder 1)
    August 7, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Voluntary Help Wanter for War on Poverty Projects, Publication (Box 69, Folder 1)
    Spring 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Quiet Revolution, Publication (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: The Quiet Revolution, Publication (Box 69, Folder 1)
- Box: 69, folder: 2 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Professional Careers in the United States Office of Education, Publication (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Handbook Office of Education Including Career Opportunities, Publication (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: New Opportunities for Typists and Stenographers in the Office of Education, Publication (Box 69, Folder 2)
- Box: 69, folder: 3 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: An Overview of Manpower Development and Training: Under Redevelopment Area Residents Program, Publication (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Programs for the Handicapped, Publication (Box 69, Folder 3)
    October 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Fact Book, Publication (Box 69, Folder 3)
    January 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: A Federal Education Agency for the Future, Publication (Box 69, Folder 3)
    April 1961. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The U.S. Office of Education: A New International Dimension, Publication (Box 69, Folder 3)
- Box: 69, folder: 4 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Program and Publications of the Office of Foreign Labor and Trade, Publication (Box 69, Folder 4)
    February 1967. Item is in English.
- Box: 69, folder: 5 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Federal Employee Unit Arbitration, Publication (Box 69, Folder 5)
- Box: 69, folder: 6 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Research Program, Publication (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Research Program, Publication (Box 69, Folder 6)
- Box: 69, folder: 7 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Organization and Personnel, Publication (Box 69, Folder 7)
    September 1941. Item is in English.
- Box: 69, folder: 8 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Hearing on Dr. Jerome B. Wiesner to be Director, Office of Science and Technology, Publication (Box 69, Folder 8)
    July 17, 1962. Item is in English.
- Box: 69, folder: 9 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Secretary's Notice: Personnel Security, Amendment No. 94, Manual of Administration, Publication (Box 69, Folder 9)
    March 11, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Secretary's Notice: Chapter 1-3, Personnel Management Evaluation, manual of Administration, Amendment No. 92, Publication (Box 69, Folder 9)
- Box: 69, folder: 10 (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: The Organization for Economic Cooperation and Development, Publication (Box 69, Folder 10)
- Box: 69, folder: 11 (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Consultation Under Executive Order 10988 Employee - Management Cooperation, Publication (Box 69, Folder 11)
- Box: 69, folder: 12 (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Guinea Mechaics' Program, Publication (Box 69, Folder 12)
- Box: 69, folder: 13 (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Model Plan for Progress, Publication (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: Plans for Progress, Publication (Box 69, Folder 13)
    August 1964-December 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Plans for Progress Program, Publication (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: Plans for Progress Program, Publication (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - Item 5: The Time is Now: A guide to effective involvment in your community's Equal Opportunity Activities, Publication (Box 69, Folder 13)
- Box: 69, folder: 14 (Box 69, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Plans for Progress: A Report, Publication (Box 69, Folder 14)
    January 1966-August 1967. Item is in English.
- Box: 69, folder: 15 (Box 69, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Information Service for Release March 20, 1963, Publication (Box 69, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: Information Service for Release March 20, 1963, Publication (Box 69, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: Equal Employment Opportunity in the U.S. Post Office Department, Publication (Box 69, Folder 15)
    April 1963. Item is in English.
- Box: 69, folder: 16 (Box 69, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Postmaster's Plan Book: Operation Teamwork, Publication (Box 69, Folder 16)
    August 1963. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Postal Service News, Publication (Box 69, Folder 16)
    February 1959. Item is in English.
- Box: 69, folder: 17 (Box 69, Folder 17)